Fire the arrows!
Tinúviel the elven-fair
Immortal maiden elven-wise
About him cast her night-dark hair
And arms like silver glimmering.
l am Arwen - l-ve come to help you.
Hear my voice...come back to the light.
Stay with the Hobbits, l-ll send horses for you.
l-m the faster rider, l-ll take him.
The Road is too dangerous.
...the power of my people will protect him.
As you wish.
Ride fast Asfaloth!
Waters of the Misty Mountains...
...listen to the great word.
Flow waters of loudwater against the ringwraiths
Waters of the Misty Mountains...
...listen to the great word.
Flow waters of loudwater against the ringwraiths
Hear my voice...come back to the light.